Hey Tyrie, welcome to New Orleans. Uh
just wanted to get your uh just kind of
thoughts on, you know, the the trade and
the Saints going and seeking you out and
bringing you here to the Big Easy.
>> Man, you know, uh first I'm grateful to
be here, grateful for the opportunity.
Um
man, I feel like I feel like here and
around the building been trying to get
this going for a while now and you know,
thankfully it finally happened. Uh, new
beginnings here. Um, glad I able to be a
saint and get this thing rolling.
>> How does it feel just knowing that, you
know, they you said that they've been
trying to get it done for a while now.
How does that feel for you just in terms
of knowing that they kind of identified
you as a, you know, a player that they
want in their building?
Uh, I mean it's always it's always a
blessing when you get to come to a place
where you're wanted and you know they're
happy about you, happy you're in the
building and you know get excited to you
know get my career going in the right
right trajectory.
>> Were you expecting this to happen on on
Saturday or was that kind of a surprise
for you?
>> Uh, no. I was I didn't know exactly what
day it was happening, but you know, I
was kind of kind of aware uh that it was
going to happen and thankfully it
happened on Saturday.
>> Arie, did you kind of need a change of
scenery?
>> Um, I wouldn't say, you know, need, but,
you know, wanted I wanted a change of
scenery.
>> Have you gotten a chance to talk to
Brandon Staley yet? And have they kind
of indicated what their vision is for
you? Uh in terms of role
>> um yes you know earlier today I met with
the whole defensive staff you know
introduced myself they introduced
theirel with me and you know really you
know they got a vision for me and the
defense uh and you know they they value
edge players. So
um they just their plan is to get me
going and you know get my best ball
going ahead of me. Harry, why
>> why do you say that you wanted a change
of scenery?
Um,
I mean, you know, I love Vegas and love
the people, love the opportunities in
Vegas, but uh I feel like wasn't off to
the best start and um pretty much
there's always a change in coaches u
every year and um I feel like here in
New Orleans the the trend is going
upward and you know I'm grateful to be
here, grateful for the opportunity.
What
>> what do you need to do uh I guess better
more consistently the most in your own
self analysis?
>> Uh
I wouldn't say change who I am, you
know, continue continue to create habits
that I have, work hard, you know, be be
a great teammate. Um
basically, it's just, you know, be
bought in and um go to work every day
and I feel like things will play itself
out.
What do you feel like it is that you
bring to Brandon Staley's defense? Um,
you know, in in with with your game.
>> Uh, you know, I I see my myself as a a
game record.
Um, you know, that's it's been a lot of
great defensive ends. There's a lot of
great defensive ends in the room. Um, I
feel like I can, um, get with them and,
you know, learn some things with them
and bring some value into the room and,
you know, be a be a dominant defensive
end for the Saints.
>> You uh, you you talked about um, the the
coaching changes in Las Vegas and and
getting this new fresh start. How
refreshing is it to to be somewhere
where there is kind of that that
stability? They ended the year strong
last year and you can kind of see where
things are going and and just overall
how refreshing is this uh new start for
you,
>> man? It's always it's always going to a
place, you know, you always anywhere you
would go, you want stability. Um, you
want people that value. You want you,
you know, you want to value people. And
I feel like this is a place that values
me and other guys like me in the room
and on the defense. And, you know, I'm
grateful that this opportunity came and,
you know, now it's just time to get to
work and make things happen.
>> You kind of mentioned it, but um, what
did you make of your first three years
in the NFL? Like, was it much different
than what you were expecting coming into
the league? How did kind of the, you
know, reality of it kind of go against
or match your expectations?
>> Um, you know, coming to the NFL, you
really don't know know how it's going to
be, but you know, I had uh great role
models around me. Uh, I had a great, you
know, great support staff there, great
defensive line coach, uh, great
defensive coordinator, you know, that
tried to bring me along the way. You
know, I made steps into the right
direction. and now it's time to make
that big leap and into a dominant pass
rusher into the in the NFL.
>> What do you think about teaming up with
another firstrounder like uh Chase
Young?
>> Uh I think it's a great thing. You know,
he I feel like, you know, we can see eye
to eye. He came from he knows what it's
like being a top pick in uh NFL. He
knows the ups, he knows the downs, and
you know, he came here, he's been been
doing doing great, of course. So, you
know, that'd be another role model by my
side and, you know, somebody that can
boost my game and learn things from.
>> Does does how things went for him since
joining New Orleans give you like a
sense of optimism about your
opportunity?
>> Um, of course, but you know, I feel like
every every player's journey in the NFL
is different. you know, I can't I can't
speak for for him. Um, you know, I
haven't really got to sit down and, you
know, pick his brain or what happened
with his situation, and he don't know
what happened in mine. So, but, you
know, what we do have in common is him
being a uh a high round defensive end, a
high pick, and you know, he came here
and he's made the best of his
opportunity, and, you know, that's what
I expect to do with mine. How did you
deal with that label of, you know, being
a high pick and um kind of was there
pressure that came along with it? Is
that something you had to get used to?
Uh just what did you make of that? I
mean, when it's a blessing to be a high,
you know, a high first round pick, a
early pick, but it's always, you always
going to have the label, you know, you
always going to you, they they look at
you as the franchise guy and they, you
know, um on the outside looking in, you
know, they the fans want you ready, you
know, immediately like the first day you
step on on the field. Uh but, you know,
it always don't it always don't work out
that way. you know, everybody
everybody's timetable in the NFL is
different. Um, but I'm glad I'm I'm
here. Uh, I'm glad for the fresh start
and I'm ready to, you know, dominate on
the field.
>> Tyrie, is there anything you've already
uh started to see improvements in that
that's helped you turn the corner that
that you identified from the first year
or two that that you've gotten better at
and and try to develop into your game?
>> Yes. Like I said earlier, you know, I
had great people around me in Las Vegas.
uh Max Crosby. I had Ron Limited as my
Dline coach. Uh would help boost my
game. Um I feel like my game has took a
big lead from you know the first two
years and you know it's continually
going up. Um
but you know stats don't make everything
but you know a lot of people look at
stats and you know I'm here to you know
play great defense and be a great
teammate and the rest of the stuff will
follow. When you look at the guys like
Cam and Chase both having two guys
double digit sacks last year, uh is that
something that also kind of excites you
about this team and your, you know, your
potential fit in this uh scheme with uh
with Brandon Staley?
>> Oh, definitely. you know, it's you
always want to see see results and when
you see, you know, them two dudes with
double digit sachs, you know, you know
that uh the coaches here have a good a
good track record and, you know, I'm
excited to fit right in and, you know,
be able to work with them and hopefully
do the same thing for myself and
hopefully, you know, continue to be with
Chase and, you know, get him to double
digit sacks again.
>> You overlap with Tyler at Texas Tech,
right? What do you remember about that
experience,
>> man? You know, me and Tyler were we both
transferred to Texas Tech. Uh, and you
know, I feel like we both left that
place better than where we found it. Um,
and to be able to team up with him, you
know, he's he's a dog. You know, he's
smart football player, always going to,
you know, come in here and work hard.
Uh, and I feel feel like that's the same
thing with me. So, I feel like we that's
why we get along with with each other.
and I'm ready to uh be his teammate
again.
>> You mentioned earlier that you had
gotten wind that the Saints were
interested in you. Could you just
provide clarity on like when that
happened? When did when did you first
get word that the Saints were kind of a
team interested in you,
>> man? Uh there's no specific timing. Uh,
you know, it's basically after the trade
happened, you know, that people tell
you, you know, you know, we we've been
trying to, you know, we've been looking
at you for a while and um, it finally
worked out. It was like, it wasn't like,
you know, I knew it when I was with the
Raiders that this thing was going to
happen. It just, you kind of hear things
after after the trade was finalized.
>> Is there a is there a I guess I'm trying
to figure out the best way to ask this.
Um, when you're a first round draft
pick, I understand that there are
coaching changes and you were looking
for a new situation, but when you're a
first-round draft pick and you're traded
for a fifth round draft pick, does that
put a chip on your shoulder in some way?
You know, I know you don't want to make
it personal, but does that motivate you
in some way?
>> Uh, I wouldn't say I wouldn't say that
motivates me. I mean, more stuff
motivates me than, you know, uh,
football things. You know, I value more
things in my my life than that. But I'm
glad that
they offered something for me and I'm
I'm here and make the best opportunity
to the what they traded for or you know
what they gave to the Raiders to get me
you know wasn't isn't what motivates me.
What motivates me I got great great
coaches I'm going to play for great uh
great organization and people that value
value me here.
Do you like that with this trade you
you're a little bit closer to home?
>> Uh I wouldn't say I home doesn't you
know I'm I've been in NFL for a minute
now so that really doesn't affect but
you know it gives opportunity for more
people to come watch you know watch me
do what I love on the field.
>> Tyrie, did you have how many defensive
coordinators did you have with with the
Raiders? Was it a different one every
year? No, I was it was the same it was
the same defensive coordinator every
year. Same Dline coach as I said
earlier. Okay.